const arr = [{"id":0,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of these conditions is easily confused with renal cell carcinoma?","answers":[{"option":"Wilm's tumor","bool":false},{"option":"Xanthogranulomatous pyelonephritis","bool":true},{"option":"Polycystic kidney disease","bool":false},{"option":"Diabetic nephropathy","bool":false},{"option":"Bladder carcinoma","bool":false}]},{"id":1,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"According to the hudood ordinance, what is the punishment of Zina liable to Hudd when both male and female are muhsan?","answers":[{"option":"10 years imprisonment","bool":false},{"option":"Five years imprisonment","bool":false},{"option":"Stoned to death","bool":true},{"option":"Hundreds strips","bool":false},{"option":"Fine not exceeding ten thousand rupees","bool":false}]},{"id":2,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Fornication under law means:","answers":[{"option":"Sexual intercourse with a woman, when the offends knows that he is not her husband","bool":false},{"option":"When the women of 21 years age have consented for the act under threat of death","bool":false},{"option":"Sexual intercourse by a women of a body under 14 years of age","bool":false},{"option":"Willful sexual intercourse between man and women who are not married to each other","bool":true},{"option":"Forced sexual intercourse by a woman with a man","bool":false}]},{"id":3,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Two adult males were convicted in the court of law for an offense of sodomy. What is the most suggestive evidence of sodomy?","answers":[{"option":"Bruising present around anal orifice","bool":false},{"option":"Loss of rugosity of anal mucosa","bool":false},{"option":"Radial fissure of mucous membrane of anus","bool":false},{"option":"Presence of semen in anal canal","bool":true},{"option":"Dilatation of anal canal","bool":false}]},{"id":4,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Anatomical waste should be disposed off in which color-coded bag?","answers":[{"option":"Blue","bool":false},{"option":"Yellow","bool":true},{"option":"Red","bool":false},{"option":"White","bool":false},{"option":"Black","bool":false}]},{"id":5,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"The type of consent recommended for examining doctors to take from the women victim of sexual assault is:","answers":[{"option":"Blanket","bool":false},{"option":"Expressed written","bool":false},{"option":"Informed written","bool":true},{"option":"Expressed oral","bool":false},{"option":"Implied","bool":false}]},{"id":6,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the most common radiolucent renal stone?","answers":[{"option":"Calcium oxalate","bool":false},{"option":"Calcium phosphate","bool":false},{"option":"Cystine stone","bool":false},{"option":"Uric acid stone","bool":true},{"option":"Ammonium magnesium phosphate","bool":false}]},{"id":7,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"A 36-year-old female presents to the emergency with a high-grade fever with chills, increased urination, and one episode of hematuria. On examination, she has tenderness in the right lumbar region. What is the most likely cause of her illness?","answers":[{"option":"Acute pyelonephritis","bool":true},{"option":"Acute salpingitis","bool":false},{"option":"Urethritis","bool":false},{"option":"Pelvic inflammatory disease","bool":false},{"option":"Nephrolithiasis","bool":false}]},{"id":8,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"A 55-year-old male comes with complaints of abdominal pain, high-grade fever with altered mental state, dysuria, and hematuria. His urine analysis report shows numerous pus cells, nitrite positive, and few red blood cells. He is diagnosed with a urinary tract infection. What would be the most common causative agent?","answers":[{"option":"Shigella species","bool":false},{"option":"Escherichia coli","bool":true},{"option":"Vibrio cholerae","bool":false},{"option":"Haemophilus influenzae","bool":false},{"option":"Moraxella species","bool":false}]},{"id":9,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is a characteristic finding of nephritic syndrome?","answers":[{"option":"Proteinuria","bool":false},{"option":"Lipiduria","bool":false},{"option":"Hematuria","bool":true},{"option":"Polyuria","bool":false},{"option":"Hypotension","bool":false}]},{"id":10,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following conditions does not favor the development of \"maceration\" in a dead fetus inside the uterine cavity?","answers":[{"option":"Dead fetus is surrounded by liqor amni","bool":false},{"option":"Membranes intact","bool":false},{"option":"Dead fetus remains inside uterus for at least 24 hours","bool":false},{"option":"Membranes ruptured","bool":true},{"option":"Fetus dies in uterus","bool":false}]},{"id":11,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which one of the following types of kidney stone formation is associated with a bacterial infection?","answers":[{"option":"Magnesium ammonium phosphate","bool":true},{"option":"Uric acid stones","bool":false},{"option":"Calcium maleate stone","bool":false},{"option":"Calcium oxalate stone","bool":false},{"option":"Calcium phosphate stone","bool":false}]},{"id":12,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the treatment of minimal change disease?","answers":[{"option":"Diuretics","bool":false},{"option":"Cephalosporins","bool":false},{"option":"Opioids","bool":false},{"option":"Corticosteroids","bool":true},{"option":"Penicillin","bool":false}]},{"id":13,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the most characteristic feature of rapidly progressive glomerulonephritis?","answers":[{"option":"Lipoid nephrosis","bool":false},{"option":"Thickened capillary loops","bool":false},{"option":"Crescent formation","bool":true},{"option":"Sub-epithelial dense deposits","bool":false},{"option":"Hyaline nodules","bool":false}]},{"id":14,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following causative organisms is responsible for xanthogranulomatous pyelonephritis?","answers":[{"option":"Salmonella","bool":false},{"option":"Neisseria gonorrhoeae","bool":false},{"option":"Proteus","bool":true},{"option":"Klebsiella","bool":false},{"option":"Escherichia coli","bool":false}]},{"id":15,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which part(s) of the Escherichia coli bacteria is responsible for causing urinary tract infection?","answers":[{"option":"Ribosome","bool":false},{"option":"Plasmid","bool":false},{"option":"Cytoplasm","bool":false},{"option":"Capsule","bool":false},{"option":"Pilli","bool":true}]},{"id":16,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the most common urinary stone present in a gout patient?","answers":[{"option":"Uric acid","bool":true},{"option":"Magnesium ammonium phosphate","bool":false},{"option":"Calcium phosphate","bool":false},{"option":"Calcium oxalate","bool":false},{"option":"Cysteine","bool":false}]},{"id":17,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the best diagnostic test for ureteric stone?","answers":[{"option":"CT scan","bool":true},{"option":"MRI scan","bool":false},{"option":"X-ray KUB","bool":false},{"option":"MRA scan","bool":false},{"option":"Ultrasound KUB","bool":false}]},{"id":18,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"A patient presented with the complaint of recurrent stones despite drinking adequate water. Which of the following is the most common renal stone?","answers":[{"option":"Magnesium ammonium phosphate","bool":false},{"option":"Calcium phosphate","bool":false},{"option":"Calcium oxalate","bool":true},{"option":"Cysteine","bool":false},{"option":"Uric acid","bool":false}]},{"id":19,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the appropriate drug of choice for a patient having renal calcium calculi?","answers":[{"option":"Spironolactone","bool":false},{"option":"Verapamil","bool":false},{"option":"Hydrochlorothiazide","bool":true},{"option":"Amoxicillin","bool":false},{"option":"Carbapenem","bool":false}]},{"id":20,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following most commonly causes acute renal failure?","answers":[{"option":"Acute tubular necrosis","bool":true},{"option":"Decreased blood flow to kidney","bool":false},{"option":"Acute interstitial nephritis","bool":false},{"option":"Polycystic kidney disease","bool":false},{"option":"Renal papillary necrosis","bool":false}]},{"id":21,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is characterized by low sperm count?","answers":[{"option":"Oligozoospermia","bool":true},{"option":"Varicoceles","bool":false},{"option":"Anejaculation","bool":false},{"option":"Retrograde ejaculation","bool":false},{"option":"Azoospermia","bool":false}]},{"id":22,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Calculate the net filtration pressure if the value of capillary pressure is 60 mm H2O, glomerular oncotic pressure is 32 mm H2O, and bowman hydrostatic pressure is 18 mm H2O.","answers":[{"option":"10 mm H2O","bool":true},{"option":"20 mm H2O","bool":false},{"option":"0 mm H2O","bool":false},{"option":"5 mm H2O","bool":false},{"option":"15 mm H2O","bool":false}]},{"id":23,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the congenital anomaly in which both the kidneys are connected by their lower poles?","answers":[{"option":"Renal agenesis","bool":false},{"option":"Polycystic kidney dsease","bool":false},{"option":"Renal hypoplasia","bool":false},{"option":"Renal dysplasia","bool":false},{"option":"Horseshoe kidney","bool":true}]},{"id":24,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following conditions is characterized by the absence of perinephric fat?","answers":[{"option":"Nephroptosis","bool":true},{"option":"Acanthosis nigricans","bool":false},{"option":"Parry-Romberg syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Lipodystrophy","bool":false},{"option":"Linear scleroderma","bool":false}]},{"id":25,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"What is lochia?","answers":[{"option":"Vaginal discharge after delivery","bool":true},{"option":"Fluid secreted by the fallopian tubes","bool":false},{"option":"Sebaceous secretions composed of sloughed-off epithelial cells","bool":false},{"option":"Purulent, foul-smelling vaginal discharge","bool":false},{"option":"Normal secretions by the vagina","bool":false}]},{"id":26,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following deposits are found in post-streptococcal glomerular nephritis?","answers":[{"option":"Granular subepithelial deposits","bool":true},{"option":"Hyaline deposits","bool":false},{"option":"Mesangial deposits","bool":false},{"option":"Subendothelial deposits","bool":false},{"option":"Ribbon-like deposits","bool":false}]},{"id":27,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"A patient was found to have immune complexes because of hepatitis B antigen. Which pattern will the deposits show?","answers":[{"option":"Mesangial deposits on immunofluorescence","bool":false},{"option":"Hyaline deposits on immunofluorescence","bool":false},{"option":"Granular deposits on immunofluorescence","bool":true},{"option":"Subepithelial deposits on immunofluorescence","bool":false},{"option":"Subendothelial deposits on immunofluorescence","bool":false}]},{"id":28,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"A patient was prescribed steroids as a treatment for nephrotic syndrome. Upon leaving steroids, the patient started having frequent relapses in 12 days. What is the probable cause of this?","answers":[{"option":"Cryoglobulinemia","bool":false},{"option":"Steroid-dependent nephritic syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"IgA nephropathy","bool":false},{"option":"Membranoproliferative glomerulonephritis","bool":false},{"option":"Steroid-dependent nephrotic syndrome","bool":true}]},{"id":29,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"A 29-year-old woman presents to the outpatient department with the complaint of joint pain in small fingers. There were no other symptoms or signs upon examination. What is the probable diagnosis of this condition?","answers":[{"option":"Systemic lupus erythematosus","bool":true},{"option":"IgA nephropathy","bool":false},{"option":"Hypertensive nephropathy","bool":false},{"option":"Cryoglobulinemia","bool":false},{"option":"Membranoproliferative glomerulonephritis","bool":false}]},{"id":30,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is a characteristic of post-streptococcal infection?","answers":[{"option":"Serum C3 levels are high","bool":false},{"option":"Proteinuria in nephritic range","bool":false},{"option":"Latency shorter after skin infection","bool":false},{"option":"Latency less than 10 days in throat infection","bool":false},{"option":"Latency longer after skin infection","bool":true}]},{"id":31,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the most common primary cause of nephrotic syndrome in adults?","answers":[{"option":"Diabetes mellitus","bool":false},{"option":"IgA nephropathy","bool":false},{"option":"Minimal change disease","bool":false},{"option":"Focal segmental glomerulosclerosis","bool":true},{"option":"Renal trauma","bool":false}]},{"id":32,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the earliest sign of capillary changes in nephrotic syndrome?","answers":[{"option":"Lipiduria","bool":false},{"option":"Increased glomerular filtration rate","bool":false},{"option":"Proteinuria","bool":true},{"option":"Decreased glomerular filtration rate","bool":false},{"option":"Hematuria","bool":false}]},{"id":33,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Papillary necrosis is a complication of pyelonephritis that is commonly seen in which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Children","bool":false},{"option":"Males","bool":false},{"option":"Females","bool":false},{"option":"Hypertensive patients","bool":false},{"option":"Diabetic patients","bool":true}]},{"id":34,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is a cardinal sign of acute pyelonephritis?","answers":[{"option":"Hematuria","bool":false},{"option":"Tubular necrosis","bool":true},{"option":"Increased glomerular filtration rate","bool":false},{"option":"Lipiduria","bool":false},{"option":"Proteinuria","bool":false}]},{"id":35,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Spalding sign is a characteristic finding of which of the following condition?","answers":[{"option":"Sodomy","bool":false},{"option":"Abortion","bool":false},{"option":"Unborn baby in the uterus","bool":false},{"option":"Maceration","bool":false},{"option":"Intrauterine dead fetus","bool":true}]},{"id":36,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"According to the Pakistan penal code, which act serves as a punishment for sodomy?","answers":[{"option":"457","bool":false},{"option":"377","bool":true},{"option":"378","bool":false},{"option":"324","bool":false},{"option":"450","bool":false}]},{"id":37,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the most common method of infanticide?","answers":[{"option":"Poisoning","bool":false},{"option":"Smothering","bool":true},{"option":"Suffocation","bool":false},{"option":"Drowning","bool":false},{"option":"Throttling","bool":false}]},{"id":38,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"A 70-year-old man was was advised to get an ultrasound done. The ultrasound report showed bilateral enlarged kidneys with multiple cysts. What is the probable diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Horseshoe kidney","bool":false},{"option":"Adult polycystic kidney disease","bool":true},{"option":"Renal calculi","bool":false},{"option":"Glomerulonephritis","bool":false},{"option":"Chronic kidney disease","bool":false}]},{"id":39,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following renal calculi deposit as a result of some genetic defect in reabsorption of amino acid by kidney?","answers":[{"option":"Magnesium ammonium phosphate","bool":false},{"option":"Calcium oxalate","bool":false},{"option":"Uric acid","bool":false},{"option":"Calcium phosphate","bool":false},{"option":"Cystine","bool":true}]},{"id":40,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"What will a person who is a habitual agent in sodomy, will have?","answers":[{"option":"Funnel shaped anus","bool":true},{"option":"Bleeding anus","bool":false},{"option":"Chestnut shaped anus","bool":false},{"option":"Bruising around the anus","bool":false},{"option":"All of the options","bool":false}]},{"id":41,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the most conclusive sign that a baby is alive upon examination by a woman medico-legal officer?","answers":[{"option":"Uterine contraction and relaxation","bool":false},{"option":"Fetal heart sounds","bool":true},{"option":"Abdomen increases in size","bool":false},{"option":"Blowing sound heard on auscultation","bool":false},{"option":"Fetal cells present in mother's blood","bool":false}]},{"id":42,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"A 5-year-old child was brought to the emergency department with complaints of abdominal pain and \r\n hematuria. Upon examination, the child had a flank palpable mass. What is the likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Renal cell carcinoma","bool":false},{"option":"Renal access","bool":false},{"option":"Renal cyst","bool":false},{"option":"Hydronephrosis","bool":false},{"option":"Wilms tumor","bool":true}]},{"id":43,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"A 7-year-old child was brought to the emergency department with complaint of hematuria. Upon examination, the child had a palpable mass in the lumbar region. What is the likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Synovial cysts","bool":false},{"option":"Spinal tumor","bool":false},{"option":"Ganglion cysts","bool":false},{"option":"Nephroblastoma","bool":true},{"option":"Myeloma","bool":false}]},{"id":44,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following conditions cannot be distinguished from chromophobe?","answers":[{"option":"Nephroblastoma","bool":false},{"option":"Sarcoma","bool":false},{"option":"Oncocytoma","bool":true},{"option":"Lymphoma","bool":false},{"option":"Renal cell carcinoma","bool":false}]},{"id":45,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following conditions present with painless gross hematuria?","answers":[{"option":"Nephroblastoma","bool":false},{"option":"Nephrolithiasis","bool":false},{"option":"Transitional cell carcinoma of bladder","bool":true},{"option":"Lymphoma","bool":false},{"option":"Wilms tumor","bool":false}]},{"id":46,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"In which of the following conditions, heavy proteinuria would be seen in an elderly man?","answers":[{"option":"Sarcoma","bool":false},{"option":"Nephroblastoma","bool":false},{"option":"Multiple myeloma","bool":true},{"option":"Hypertension","bool":false},{"option":"Renal cell carcinoma","bool":false}]},{"id":47,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following features suggests intrinsic renal failure?","answers":[{"option":"Potassium excretion greater than 1 percent","bool":false},{"option":"Sodium excretion greater than 1 percent","bool":true},{"option":"Chloride excretion greater than 1 percent","bool":false},{"option":"Lipid excretion greater than 1 percent","bool":false},{"option":"Hematuria greater than 1 percent","bool":false}]},{"id":48,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"A patient underwent transurethral resection of the prostate and developed transient stroke and altered consciousness. Which of the following is the probable cause?","answers":[{"option":"Hyperkalemia","bool":false},{"option":"Hypokalemia","bool":false},{"option":"Hypernatremia","bool":false},{"option":"Hyponatremia","bool":false},{"option":"TUR syndrome","bool":true}]},{"id":49,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following surgical procedure is preferred for prostatectomy?","answers":[{"option":"Percutaneous nephrolithotomy","bool":false},{"option":"Ureteroscopy","bool":false},{"option":"Lithotripsy","bool":false},{"option":"Transurethral resection of the prostate","bool":true},{"option":"Nephrectomy","bool":false}]},{"id":50,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following characterizes the syndrome of inappropriate antidiuretic hormone secretion?","answers":[{"option":"Hypotonic euvolemic hypernatremia","bool":false},{"option":"Hypertonic hypervolemic hyponatremia","bool":false},{"option":"Hypotonic euvolemic hyponatremia","bool":true},{"option":"Hypotonic hypervolemic hyponatremia","bool":false},{"option":"Hypertonic euvolemic hyponatremia","bool":false}]},{"id":51,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the treatment of hypernatremia of a patient with chronic liver disease and ascites?","answers":[{"option":"Diuretics and water restriction","bool":false},{"option":"Normal saline","bool":false},{"option":"Diuretics only","bool":true},{"option":"Ringer lactate","bool":false},{"option":"Water restriction only","bool":false}]},{"id":52,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following should not be given to a patient of hypernatremia?","answers":[{"option":"Hypertonic 3% saline","bool":true},{"option":"Hypertonic 5% saline","bool":false},{"option":"Hypertonic 4% saline","bool":false},{"option":"Hypertonic 1% saline","bool":false},{"option":"Hypertonic 2% saline","bool":false}]},{"id":53,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Hyperchloremic metabolic acidosis is a side-effect seen in patients treated with which of the following drug?","answers":[{"option":"Acetazolamide","bool":true},{"option":"Indapamide","bool":false},{"option":"Chlorothiazide","bool":false},{"option":"Metolazone","bool":false},{"option":"Chlorthalidone","bool":false}]},{"id":54,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the most common risk factor for dialysis and transplant?","answers":[{"option":"Muscle cramping","bool":false},{"option":"Difficulty sleeping","bool":false},{"option":"Heart disease","bool":true},{"option":"Asthma","bool":false},{"option":"Sepsis","bool":false}]},{"id":55,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"A sample was taken from a raped woman's vagina. Upon testing, there was an absence of sperm. Which test will detect and confirm the presence of semen?","answers":[{"option":"Saline solution test","bool":false},{"option":"Acid phosphatase test","bool":true},{"option":"Colposcopy","bool":false},{"option":"Vaginitis test","bool":false},{"option":"Vaginal swab test","bool":false}]},{"id":56,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"A patient presents with cardiac failure complications and edema. The best drug of choice acts on which portion of kidney?","answers":[{"option":"Proximal convoluted tubule","bool":false},{"option":"Thin ascending limp of loop of Henle","bool":false},{"option":"Dscending limp of loop of Henle","bool":false},{"option":"Thick ascending limp of loop of Henle","bool":true},{"option":"Distal convoluted tubule","bool":false}]},{"id":57,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which is the best diuretic given for acute treatment of comatose patient with cerebral edema?","answers":[{"option":"Mannitol","bool":true},{"option":"Metolazone","bool":false},{"option":"Chlorthalidone","bool":false},{"option":"Indapamide","bool":false},{"option":"Hydrochlorothiazide","bool":false}]},{"id":58,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the characteristic difference between a false virgin and a true virgin?","answers":[{"option":"Narrow vagina","bool":false},{"option":"Non rugosity of vaginal wall","bool":false},{"option":"Wide vaginal wall","bool":false},{"option":"Hymen edges undulated plus 2 fingers inserted","bool":true},{"option":"Funnel shaped vagina","bool":false}]},{"id":59,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Paresthesia, nausea, and metabolic acidosis are the side effects seen in which of the following drugs?","answers":[{"option":"Chlorthalidone for high blood pressure","bool":false},{"option":"Amiloride for high potassium levels","bool":false},{"option":"Acetazolamide for glaucoma","bool":true},{"option":"Furosemide for edema","bool":false},{"option":"Bumetanide for heart failure","bool":false}]},{"id":60,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the first thing we do while examining rape victim?","answers":[{"option":"Analyze for evidence","bool":false},{"option":"Inquire about the incident","bool":false},{"option":"Examine the vagina","bool":false},{"option":"Ensure privacy","bool":true},{"option":"Record the preliminary data","bool":false}]},{"id":61,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the characteristic feature of vagitus uterinus?","answers":[{"option":"Baby delivered enclosed in amniotic sac","bool":false},{"option":"Unborn baby crying in uterus","bool":true},{"option":"Preeclampsia","bool":false},{"option":"Ectopic pregnancy","bool":false},{"option":"Placenta previa","bool":false}]},{"id":62,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Hyperplastic arteriolitis is seen in which of the following conditions?","answers":[{"option":"Hypertensive nephropathy","bool":true},{"option":"Hypertension","bool":false},{"option":"Diabetes","bool":false},{"option":"Systemic lupus erythematosus","bool":false},{"option":"Syndrome of inappropriate antidiuretic hormone secretion","bool":false}]},{"id":63,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"Which of the following is the second most common organism that causes recurrent urinary tract infection?","answers":[{"option":"Clostridium difficile","bool":false},{"option":"Enterococcus faecalis","bool":false},{"option":"Pseudomonas aeruginosa","bool":false},{"option":"Staphylococcus saprophyticus","bool":true},{"option":"Escherichia coli","bool":false}]},{"id":64,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2019","question":"A newborn baby is brought to the outpatient department with the complaint of constant urine dribbling. Upon ultrasound, there is bilateral hydronephrosis and the bladder is full. What is the probable diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Posterior urethral valve","bool":true},{"option":"Renal stones","bool":false},{"option":"Diabetic nephropathy","bool":false},{"option":"Membranoproliferative glomerulonephritis","bool":false},{"option":"Overflow incontinence","bool":false}]}]
export default arr